让我们从应用程序开始。
Let's start with the application.
怎么把你的脚踩在门里
How to get your foot in the door?
最初，我不知道，调查，也许我想开始研究。
That initial, I don't know, probe into,
maybe I want to start looking around.
也许我想看看这家公司的情况
Maybe I wanna see what
this company is about.
也许我想看看他们是否注意到我的申请
Maybe I wanna see if they even notice
me if I put in my application.
我有一些小费
I've got some tips on that.
在你申请之前的第一件事，甚至在考虑申请之前，
The first thing before you even apply,
even before you think about applying,
你觉得你现在的工作怎么样
think, what do you like
about your current job?
是，是学习环境，人友善吗 ?
Is it, it's a learning environment and
people are friendly?
是你解决这些难以置信的复杂挑战吗 ? 它很有价值吗 ?
Is it you solve these incredibly complex
challenges and it's very rewarding?
是免费的吗
Is it the free food?
贵公司的工程文化有很多吗 ?
Is it your company has a lot of
notoriety as an engineering culture?
想一想你现在的工作是什么样的 ?
Think about what do you like
about your current job?
然后想想，我接下来要做什么 ?
And then think,
what do I want in my next job?
这很重要
That's important.
很多时候我们盲目地向公司申请
A lot of times we apply it blindly
to companies just trying to see
我们将在那里降落我们不向它方向
where we'll land and
we don't do it with direction.
我们不是故意的
We don't do with purpose.
我们不认为我想做下一份工作但你没得到任何想法
We don't think I wanna be at this next
job, but you didn't get any thoughts.
你受雇来工作一年你就像我不开心
You get hired, you work there for
a year and you're like I am unhappy.
然后你再这样做，然后你再做一次，而不是让我们
And then you do that again, and
then you do that again, rather than, let's
找到一个你知道你可以成长的家，你可以建造，你可以学习。
find a home where you know you can grow
and you can build and you could learn.
而随着时间的推移你说我很满意我可以向上移动
And over time you say I'm very satisfied,
I can move up the ladder,
我可以制造凉爽的东西
I can build cool things.
我只是有很多工作满足感
I just have a lot of job satisfaction.
大多数人都不这么做
Most people don't do that.
因为采访是一种crap枪战。
Because interviewing is
kind of a crapshoot.
我们只是希望我们能在某个地方找到工作
We just hope we get a job somewhere.
但是当你申请工作时，我鼓励你，
But I encourage you when you're applying
for job, do it with intentionality,
是为了达到目的
do it with a purpose.
我想在这家公司工作这就是原因
Say, I wanna work at this company,
and here's why.
还有什么公司对工程文化有吸引力 ?
Also what companies have
appealing engineering cultures?
是你的公司吗
Is it your company?
新闻里读到的公司吗
Is it the companies you
read about in the news?
你觉得有公司不好吗，你觉得有公司好吗 ?
Are there companies you think are bad,
are there companies you think are good?
仔细想想，因为工程文化真的很重要，
Consider that carefully, because
engineering culture is really important,
我们从不集中精力
and we never focus on it.
我们关注的是工作，而不是，我是否会为下一份工作感到高兴 ?
We focus on getting the job, rather than,
will I be happy this next job?
文化是和我一起的吗
Does the culture vibe with me?
我可以说，事实上有一些公司是我不喜欢工作的
And I can say for a fact there are
companies that I would not enjoy working
啊，大公司，他们花了我很多钱，但是在那里我不高兴。
at, big companies, they pay me a lot of
money, but I wouldn't be happy there.
如果你不打算做任何事情
And what's the point of doing any
of this if you're not gonna be
很高兴你做了什么
happy doing what you do?